大家好 我是Bob Tabor
这里是 www.learnvisualstudio.et
Hi I'm Bob Tabor with www.learnvisualstudio.net
今天我要讲的是第三个challenge（思考题）
I'm here with the third challenge
将将！复杂布局
the Laborious Layout Challenge
这个要比之前的难一点哟 因为你要同时用到
this one is a little bit trickier because u're gonna use
多种的Grids 和StackPanels
both multiple Grids and multiple StackPanels
而且可能会有很多种不同的办法来解题
and there're probably a number of different
ways to solve this, not just one way
我们先来看一下这个题，你可以看到
let's take a look of the challenge itself, u can see that
这里出现了用title（题目）区分开的三个不同部分
we've got three sections, each section starts with a title
这三个title都竖向排列于文字内容的开端
the title is offset vertically from the text that is associate with
在每段文字内容的下方
below each section of text
有不同颜色的三个长方形
there's a little flag like area with three rectangle with different colors
还有一点需要我想提醒大家的是\I guess the last thing I want to point out is that
界面左侧和每个部分间都留有空白
there's some margin space on the left and here between each of the title area
所以我们一起来看看题目要求吧( •̀ ω •́ )✧
so let's take a look the rules for this challenge
首先，要记得把Girds和StackPanels都用上哟
first of all, u have to use both Grids and StackPanels
就算你觉得自己厉害的可以只有两个中的一个
even if u think u can just use the StackPanels or Grids
其实我让你两个一起用就是为了证明---其实一起用是不行的╮(╯-╰)╭
no, i'm forcing u to use both together just to
prove that point--- u can't use together
接下来， 我又一次把界面设置成了
secondly, here again, I set the designer
电脑桌面大小而不是手机桌面，这样我就有了更多的横向空间
at the desktop not the phone size, just so I get more horizontal space
下一个要求就是
the next requirement
整个界面的宽度应该是500个像素点
the width of the entire layout should be 500 pixels
所以从左侧到右侧
so from this side hereon the left to this side here on the right
不要担心右侧的空白部分（大丈夫！）
u will notice that they give us a lot of extra space on the right ,that's ok
反正就是道练习题嘛
this is just a challenge, is not real life.
第四点，这个任务来自LoremIpsum.txt file
No.4, the task comes from the LoremIpsum.txt file
我觉得你需要的只是其中开头部分
i think all u need is the very first line of LoremIpsum.txt file
不需要看整篇
there's like a 5 lines paragraph rather
只要看第一段就好咯
u just need the first paragraph